export const {colorData, colorData2, colorData3, colorData4, colorData5, colorData6, colorData7, colorData8} = {
    colorData: [
        { back: '#5990FC', front: 'white' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: 'white' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#242A30' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: 'white' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: '#5990FC', front: '#242A30' },
    ],
    colorData2: [
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#D2E2FE' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#D2E2FE' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: 'white', front: '#D2E2FE' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' }
    ],
    colorData3: [
        { back: '#5990FC', front: '#D2E3FE' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: '#5990FC', front: '#D2E2FE' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: '#5990FC', front: '#D2E2FE' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' }
    ],
    colorData4: [
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' },
        { back: '#D2E2FE', front: 'white' }
    ],
    colorData5: [
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#242A30' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#242A30' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: '#5990FC' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#242A30' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#242A30' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#242A30', front: '#5990FC' },
    ],
    colorData6: [
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
        { back: '#FFFFFF', front: '#D3E2FD' },
        { back: '#D3E2FD', front: '#FFFFFF' },
    ],
    colorData7: [
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
        { back: '#D3E3FD', front: '#5C93F9' },
        { back: '#5C93F9', front: '#D3E3FD' },
    ],
    colorData8: [
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
        { back: '#D3E2F9', front: '#262B2F' },
        { back: '#262B2F', front: '#D3E2F9' },
    ]

}
